

Maxim

Huryanov

Experience

Feb 2016–March 2017 PHP/Javascript Developer● Full-stack developer ● Redwerk

March 2017–August 2019
RoR/Python Developer • Full-stack developer • GBKSOFT

Summary

I am a full stack web developer having rich experience in software development. I worked as a full-stack developer for several local companies from small to early startups. My deep full-stack experience includes Python and Frameworks such as Django and Flask Also, I have good knowledge of Javascript-based Frontends like Angular, Vue, and React.js, and Ruby on Rails. Also, I am familiar with the various Javascript libraries: Jquery, Google Map API, ArcGIS, D3, Plotly.js, Leafly.js, Chart.js, HighChart.js I strive to achieve quality, correctness, performance, and maintainability in all products I write. I believe the application of solid software engineering principles is imperative and allows me to be flexible enough to handle any sort of programming task. I have experienced several online services – AWS, GCP, Firebase, Azure, Github, Trello and Notion

0

Molodizhna 5 Horodok, Rivne Oblast 35331 Ukraine



https://www.behance.ne t/maximhn



https://www.linkedin.co m/in/maxim-huryanovba9499216/



https://github.com/mhur
yanov/



https://mhuryanov.githu b.io/

Education

NUWM Technical College, Ukraine

 I have studied computer mathematics majoring in starting from C++/C#/Python.

National University of Water And Environmental Engineering, Ukraine

I have studied computer science majoring in web development with PHP(Laravel, Codeigniter, Wordpress), Javascript(React, Angular, Vue and Node.js) and Python(Django and Flask) frameworks and Ruby on Rails.



Portfolios

(Some of my works, not all)

• 2016.7 ~ 2016.9 Apex Angular Theme

Link: https://pixinvent.com/apex-angular-4-bootstrap-admin-

template/demo-1/

Role: Front-end developer

• 2016.11 ~ 2017.1 Rubick Vue Theme

Link: http://rubick-vue.left4code.com/

Role: Front-end developer

• 2017.3 ~ 2017.6 Boon Supply

Link: https://boonsupply.com

Role: Full stack developer

• 2017.9 ~ 2018.9 Contingent

Link: https://contingent.ai/

Role: Full stack developer

• 2018.11 ~ 2019.2 E. Marsh Upholsterers

Link: https://www.e-marsh.co.uk/

Role: Full stack developer

2019.5 ~ 2020.5 Preloved

Link: https://preloved.co.uk/

Role: Full stack developer

• 2020.8 ~ 2021.4 Scribble Together

Link: https://scribbletogether.com/

Role: Full stack developer

